(Raj:)And when he got food poisoning
at the Rose Bowl parade...
(Raj:)...he begged a deity he doesn't believe in
to end his life quickly.
(Sheldon:)Do you understand
how important Hawking is to me?
When I was 6 years old,
l dressed up as him for Halloween.
- You're kidding.
- No, sir.
(Sheldon:)No, I took my dad's desk chair,
attached a Speak & Spell to it...
(Sheldon:)...and made my sister push me up
and down the block to trick-or-treat.
(Sheldon:)Granted, most people thought I was
R2-D2, but still, I got a lot of candy.
(Howard:)You don't seem to be understanding
the English word "no."
(Howard:)Maybe a different language will help.
Russian: Nyet. Chinese: bú.
Japanese: iie. Klingon: qo'.
Binary coded ASCll:
0110111001101111.
- It's actually 011011110...
- No!